───────────────────────────────────────
Parallax Propeller Chip Project Archive
───────────────────────────────────────

 Project :  "Demo_Regular_74HC595"

Archived :  Tuesday, April 21, 2009 at 1:00:02 AM

    Tool :  Propeller Tool version 1.2.5


            Demo_Regular_74HC595.spin
              │
              ├──74HC595_Regular.spin
              │
              └──TV_Text.spin
                   │
                   └──TV.spin


────────────────────
Parallax, Inc.
www.parallax.com
support@parallax.com
USA 916.624.8333

Reference:
http://obex.parallax.com/object/102

Description from Reference:
Easily control several 74HC595 shift registers in series. Now includes a variation which leaves out the PWM feature and instead supports up to 100 chips! Still also includes the multi-PWM driver, which allows you to set PWM frequency and duty cycle for any or all of 32 outputs. The PWM driver remembers whether you've set an output to PWM or a steady high or low value, and manages the PWM outputs for you automatically. Also includes the version 1.0 Simple_74HC595 object for those who just want to understand how to shift data out to the 74HC595 chip.
 
If you downloaded the version 2.0 or 2.1 driver, you should download and replace it with the new version 2.2 driver, which has some bugs fixed; see the release notes at the top of the 74HC595_MultiPWM.spin file for detailed information.